

A 20 Via Lucca C116, Irvine, CA 92612

M 1 352 552 7216

E lindsay.codes@gmail.com

Summary

I have experience working and leading cross functional teams in Design Research, UX & UI Design, and Front-End Development. I've owned projects, facilitated workshops, and consulted for teams at IBM, McGraw Hill, and Astral AR. I am currently taking on supplemental work to finance higher education.

Education

Northcentral University 2017-Present *School of Business*Master Degree in Business Administration

Full Sail University 2012-2015

Design and Development Degree Program

Bachelor of Science

3.8 GPA Average

6 Course Director Awards

Professional Skills

UX/UI Design

Adobe Creative Cloud Prototyping Tools (Axure, InVision, etc.) Design Research Multivariate (A/B) Testing

Software Development

HTML5, CSS3, SASS JavaScript, NodeJS, PHP, Python MySQL, MongoDB APIs (Consuming & Developing) Libraries & Frameworks React, Electron, Express, Laravel, etc.

Branding & Identity Digital Marketing

Work Experience

Astral AR, LLC 2017-Present Director of User Experience

Responsible for the end-to-end user experience. Actively implements design strategies that cater to the needs of customers and stakeholders.

McGraw-Hill Education 2017

Lead User Experience Designer

Collaborated on cross-functional teams to deliver a holistic experience for various educational applications.

IBM Design 2015-2017 *Software Designer*

Prototyped, collaborated, and consulted on multiple software products (including Bluemix). Gained experience in leadership, mentoring, and information architecture.

Platinum Advisor Strategies 2013-2014 *Graphic Designer*

Designed and coordinated branding materials for Platinum clients. Customized and created website elements for client content management systems. Lead email marketing campaigns.

Personal Skills

Communication Ideation Collaboration Activation Commitment Dedication Brainstorming Innovation

^{*}I am a bit of a **Maverick**.;)